A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Politics - New York City Office, Series J.1 FA345
Rockefeller Archive Center
- New York State Gubernatorial Campaigns, 1958-1970; 3; 33 Document Box(es)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Questions and Answers (Box 52, Folder 570)
    NAR positions on various issues affecting New York State.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Reports - "Organizational Analysis and Vote History" (Box 52, Folder 571)
    Voter survey for New York State election districts.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Reports - Task Force on Middle Income Housing (Box 52, Folder 572)
    Copies of 2nd and final report.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Republican Clubs - New York City & New York State (Box 53, Folder 573)
    Invitations to NAR requesting appearances at club affairs; state officers of Young Republicans National Federation; association of New York State Young Republican Clubs.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Republican State Committee - Materials (Box 53, Folder 574)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Republican State Committee - Members (Box 53, Folder 575)
    Book containing all members of the Republican State Committee, including notations of those that have met NAR.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Republican State Committee - Memoranda (Box 53, Folder 576)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Research (Box 53, Folder 577)
    Reports of activity of research group; campaign pledges, promises & commitments of NAR as of September 27, 1958.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Rockland for Rockefeller Committee (Box 53, Folder 578)
    NAR correspondence with members of the Rockland for Rockefeller Committee.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Sandler, John J. (Box 53, Folder 579)
    Text of address by Sandler at the 62nd Annual Convention of the Allied Printing Trades Council, July 9, 1958.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Speeches - Speeches and Drafts (Box 53, Folder 580)
    Excerpts from NAR speeches: New York State Association of Young Republicans; New York economy; Order of the Eastern Star; Letters of appreciation for NAR's speech appearances.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Speeches - August 1958 (Box 53, Folder 581)
    Speech at New York State Fair, acceptance speech at convention.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Speeches - September 1-15, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 582)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Speeches - September 16-30, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 583)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Speeches - October 1-8, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 584)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Speeches - October 4, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 585)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Speeches - October 9-14, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 586)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Speeches - October 15-16, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 587)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Speeches - October 17-20, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 588)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Speeches - October 21-22, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 589)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Speeches - October 23-31, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 590)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Speeches - November 1-3, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 591)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Statements (Box 55, Folder 592)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Statements of Policy (Box 55, Folder 593)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Statement on Running for Governorship, June 30, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 594)
    Draft copies of NAR statement re acceptance of Republican nomination if chosen, includes NAR's reading copy. Dr. Franz Winkler's comments on speech working & importance of rhythms in spoken & written word as factor in public guidance.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Stationery (Box 55, Folder 595)
    Samples of letterhead for "Nelson A. Rockefeller for Governor" and "Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating."
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Telegrams to Chairmen, November 2, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 596)
    NAR telegrams of confidence to campaign chairmen.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Television/Radio (Box 55, Folder 597)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Television/Radio Appearances (Box 55, Folder 598)
    Correspondence re: NAR television appearances & telecasts, radio interviews.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - United Republican Finance Committee (Box 55, Folder 599)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Volunteer Information (Box 55, Folder 600)
    List of volunteers who worked at 19 W. 50th St.; NAR letters of appreciation.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Voting Statistics, 1954 and 1958 (Box 55, Folder 601)
    New York Gubernatorial Election voting statistics - anticipated vote for 1958, compared with 1954, actual and by county. Percentage of registered voters who voted; delegates to state conventions; U.S. senator; House of Representatives.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Washington Square Controversy (Box 55, Folder 602)
    Material concerning the permanent closing of Washington Square Park to traffic.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Wilson, Malcolm (Box 55, Folder 603)
    2nd report of Joint Legislative Committee on Sabbath Law, 1953; copies of resolution adopted at annual convention of New York State Department of the American Legion, North Hempstead Republican Committee, 1958-1959; R. B. Williams report on campaign activities.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Young Republican Clubs (Box 55, Folder 604)
    New York Young Republican Club Directory; endorsement of NAR by New York club.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Alexander Halpern File (Box 56, Folder 605)
    Financial statements, state activities, mobile unit, special groups J. V. Gibson, special groups - S. R. Walker, platform rallies, photographic report, master file.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Biographies (Box 56, Folder 606)
    Brief biographies of Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, Sen. Jacob E. Javits, Louis J. Lefkowitz.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Films (Box 56, Folder 607)
    Correspondence concerning various films for 1962 campaign.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Financing (Box 56, Folder 608)
    Politics, parties & pressure groups; campaign expenditure.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Literature (Box 56, Folder 609)
    NAR for Governor printed material; "Why I Am A Republican" by J. Javits.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Material (Box 56, Folder 610)
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Material (Box 56, Folder 611)
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Material, Requests (Box 56, Folder 612)
    Requests for campaign literature, buttons, etc. & orders filled.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Summary Statement, November 4, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 613)
    November 4, 1962 campaign summary statement made by NAR.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Candidate List Requests (Box 56, Folder 614)
    Requests for names & addresses of all candidates who filed to run as Republicans for state & Congressional offices; Queens County candidates for 1962; Onondaga County; October 1962 Survey of Voting Record of Incumbent Democratic Assemblymen, 1961-1962.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Clippings & Releases (Box 56, Folder 615)
    Republican National Committee "Battle Line" newsletters; miscellaneous articles & editorials re NAR campaign; two copies of November 1962 "Advance."
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Committees - General (Box 57, Folder 616)
    Comments of various prominent Democratic candidates on the candidacy of New York City District Attorney Morgenthau; letters of support for NAR, committees for NAR's re-election; L. Judson Morhouse letter with bios of 3 attorneys for possible appointment as judge of the Court of General Sessions of County of New York.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Committees - Arts & Sciences (Box 57, Folder 617)
    Support for NAR by committee of educators & scientists.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Committees - Builders for Rockefeller (Box 57, Folder 618)
    Wayne E. Edwards, state chairman; letters re election of NAR.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Committees - Business & Industry Committee (Box 57, Folder 619)
    Names suggested for Business & Industry Committee.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Committees - Citizens Committee for Rockefeller-Javits (Box 57, Folder 620)
    Form letter requesting support for Citizens for Rockefeller-Javits; memo on meeting re consolidated campaign & budget for New York State.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Committees - Lawyers for Rocky (Box 57, Folder 621)
    Lawyers Committee for the Republican Ticket; Lawyers Committee for the Rockefeller Team.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Committees - New York Young Republican Club (Box 57, Folder 622)
    Letters of invitation to attend Campaign Kick-Off; recording of Rockefeller Campaign Song.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Committees - Young GOP (Box 57, Folder 623)
    Schedule for All American Conference - Youth Wants To Know; memorandum re Judicial District.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Congratulatory Letter (Box 57, Folder 624)
    List of congratulatory messages to NAR, breakdown by individual states & groups.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Conservative Party (Box 57, Folder 625)
    Opposition to Rockefeller-Javits. List of active Conservative Clubs in New York State; text of WSYR-TV program (Syracuse) on David Jaquith; 1962 Morhouse memos re Conservative Party; excerpts concerning conservatism from keynote address by Walter J. Mahoney at opening session of Republican State Convention.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Contributions (Box 57, Folder 626)
    Contribution made by D. Stroud; NAR's appreciation.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 627)
    Correspondence regarding campaign for re-election: campaign staff, budgets, committees, broadcasts; letters of appreciation for NAR support; request by NE radio network to broadcast proceedings of Republican Convention; NAR live TV appearances; requests for NAR TV & radio appearances; TV coverage of convention by various networks; committee members on assembly district.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 628)
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - County Endorsements (Box 57, Folder 629)
    Endorsements by Warren County Republican Committee and Bronx County Republican Committee.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Editorial Endorsements (Box 57, Folder 630)
    Clippings of newspaper endorsements; editorial endorsements.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Editorial Endorsements (Box 57, Folder 631)
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Election Statement, November 5, 1962 (Box 57, Folder 632)
    November 5, 1962 statement issued by William J. Pfeiffer.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Hall, Leonard W. (Box 57, Folder 633)
    Letter to Judson Morhouse on splinter parties.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Javits, Jacob (Box 58, Folder 634)
    Salute to Javits, rundown of timetable; photo of Javits; clippings re his re-election to the Senate.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Kick-Off Program (Box 58, Folder 635)
    Republican Kick-Off Dinner; TV shows, Victory Vanguard, WNEW-TV.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - McCann-Marschalk Advertising Agency (Box 58, Folder 636)
    New York Republican State Committee cash flow statement as of September 21, 1962; October 5, 1962 status report on promotional materials; NAR radio & TV spots; advertising, campaign slogans, media estimates, contact reports & office memos.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - McCann-Marschalk Advertising Agency (Box 58, Folder 637)
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - McCann-Marschalk Advertising Agency (Box 58, Folder 638)
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - McCann-Marschalk Advertising Agency (Box 58, Folder 639)
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - McCann-Marschalk Advertising Agency (Box 58, Folder 640)
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - McCann-Marschalk Advertising Agency (Box 58, Folder 641)
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Pfeiffer, William L. (Box 59, Folder 642)
    Michael J. Scelsi [appointments secretary] memos to Pfeiffer re campaign projects status report & re 1958 campaign newspaper advertising.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Publicity - American Heritage Spots (Box 59, Folder 643)
    Transcripts for commercials. NAR, Art Linkletter "Vote" campaign; NAR - "Register Now & Vote" spots; Radio & TV spot by Jacqueline Kennedy.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Publicity - Ask Governor Rockefeller (Box 59, Folder 644)
    Transcripts of interviews, October 23, 1962 by WKBW-TV in Buffalo; October 25, 1962 by WRGB-TV in Schenectady.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Publicity - League Television Programs (Box 59, Folder 645)
    Tentative schedule for League sponsored pre-election TV programs on WNBC.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Publicity - "Let's Find Out" (Box 59, Folder 646)
    Transcript of WCBS radio program.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Republican Platform (Box 59, Folder 647)
    Republican Party Platform for 1962 & additions.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Rural Citizens for Rockefeller (Box 59, Folder 648)
    Rural Citizen Proposed Program; Media Estimate Rural Citizens for Rockefeller.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Schwartz, Arthur (Box 59, Folder 649)
    Counsel to the New York Republican State Committee; miscellaneous material, bulletins.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Telethons (Box 59, Folder 650)
    Excerpts of remarks by NAR re Republican women in industry & professions; excerpts from Wilma Rogalin speech "To the Business & Professional Women of Albany."
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Women's Activities (Box 59, Folder 651)
    "Citizens for Rockefeller-Javits" folder; women's activities; "Call for Good Government."
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Women's Division (Box 59, Folder 652)
    Memo re Summary of Women's Division Expenses for the 1962 Campaign Projects.
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Boyer, Louise A. - Minutes of Meetings (Box 59, Folder 653)
    Minutes of campaign staff meetings; Ronan memorandum on "campaign strategy & its implementation to date."
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Materials (Box 59, Folder 654)
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Clippings (Box 59, Folder 655)
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Committees, 1966-1967 (Box 59, Folder 656)
    Memo concerning the status & additional budgetary needs of New York City campaign; NAR thank you's for service in campaigns.
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Congratulatory Letters, 1966-1967 (Box 59, Folder 657)
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Contributions, 1966-1967 (Box 59, Folder 658)
    NAR letters of gratitude for contributions.
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Election Night Invitations (Box 60, Folder 659)
    Invitations for election night party at New York Hilton.
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Election Night Invitations (Box 60, Folder 660)
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Gubernatorial Campaign Archives (Box 60, Folder 661)
    Campaign structure; 2 copies of 55th Street campaign files.
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Gubernatorial Campaign Archives (Box 60, Folder 662)
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Gubernatorial Campaign Archives (Box 60, Folder 663)
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Invitations, declined (Box 60, Folder 664)
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Miscellaneous (A-Z) (Box 60, Folder 665)
    Miscellaneous file of NAR thank you's for endorsements, memos, bill payment reminders; NAR letters of appreciation for foreign cables & letters of congratulations.
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Report: Anatomy of a Big city Campaign (Box 61, Folder 666)
    Bound report on NAR's 1966 campaign in New York City.
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Republican State Convention (Box 61, Folder 667)
    NAR letters of appreciation for work done on convention; appreciation for support (speeches).
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Republican Finance Committee Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 669)
    NAR letters of appreciation for contributions & service on campaign committee.
  - 1966 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Rodgers Book (Box 61, Folder 670)
    "Syracuse Herald" article, July 10, 1966, "Rocky Ducks His Sales Tax," statement for "Syracuse Herald Journal," July 12, 1966.
  - 1970 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Gifts (Box 61, Folder 671)
    List of campaign workers and volunteers to receive memento to commemorate the campaign.
  - 1970 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Gifts (Box 61, Folder 672)
  - 1970 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Materials (Box 61, Folder 673)
  - 1970 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Clippings (Box 61, Folder 674)
  - 1970 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Contributions (Box 61, Folder 675)
  - 1970 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Memos, G. L. Hinman (Box 61, Folder 676)
    Memo to NAR regarding NAR's involvement in the "Library of Presidential Papers."
  - 1970 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Printed Materials (Box 61, Folder 677)
- Polls, 1958-1970; 4; 6 Document Box(es)
  Subseries 4 is arranged broadly by the campaign/term for which the polls were conducted.
  This subseries contains a selection of polls and public opinion surveys conducted primarily in New York State, although a small selection concerns national issues. In most cases the polls were conducted by Political Analysis Associates of Princeton, New Jersey. Primarily, the surveys focus on Governor Rockefeller or are specific to an issue within New York State. However, some were undertaken in response to New York City issues, such as two surveys conducted in 1970 on the status of the New York City subway system and a phone survey of New York City Mayor John Lindsay's popularity. In some cases, accompanying memoranda may be found that analyze the poll data for the Governor. Note that this subseries is an incomplete aggregate of the polls conducted in New York State.
  - Bachelder, 1958-1961 (Box 62, Folder 678)
    Polls by Bachelder & New York Republican State Committee, 1958; payment made for Bachelder polls.
  - New York State, 1958-1959 (Box 62, Folder 679)
    Political survey of New York; "New York Times" poll; questions asked, tabulation of results.
  - New York State, 1958-1959 (Box 62, Folder 680)
  - New York State, 1958-1959 (Box 62, Folder 681)
  - Public Opinion Polls, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 682)
    New York Survey, May 1959; Six States Survey, October 1959; Oregon Issues, November 1959; Campaign Strategy, December 1959.
  - Public Opinion Polls, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 683)
    Political Situation in New York State, February 1960; voters in California, Illinois, New York, Pennsylvania & Texas, July 1960; New York State Political Surveys, October 1960.
  - Public Opinion Polls, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 684)
  - Public Opinion Polls, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 685)
    New York State Political Survey, February 1961; 1961 Election in New York City, April 1961; Governors Program - New York State, July 1961; New York City-Mayoralty, September & October 1961; Fallout Shelters, November 1961.
  - Public Opinion Polls, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 686)
  - New York City Mayoralty Poll, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 687)
    Survey on possibility of Republican victory in New York City.
  - Lubell, Samuel - Study - 1961 New York City Mayoralty Campaign (Box 63, Folder 688)
    Study of New York City Mayoralty race & strategy for campaign.
  - Public Opinion Polls, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 689)
    New York Liquor Law Survey, January 1962; 40th Congressional District, New York, June 1962; Government Operations Study, August 1962; State Legislation, September 1962.
  - 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign (Box 63, Folder 690)
  - Public Opinion Polls, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 691)
    Post Election Study - selected New York counties, January 1963; correspondence 3/63-12-63, Lloyd Free to NAR commenting on polls taken. Kennedy image, assassination.
  - Public Opinion Polls, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 692)
  - New Hampshire Poll, November 1963 (Box 63, Folder 693)
  - Public Opinion Polls, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 694)
  - Convention - New York State Voter Inventory Study, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 695)
    Bennett-Chaikin, Inc. poll.
  - California, May 1964 (Box 64, Folder 696)
    Resurvey of GOP voters, California.
  - California, March 1964 (Box 64, Folder 697)
    Men & Issues GOP Survey
  - Oregon, April 1964 (Box 64, Folder 698)
    Resurvey of GOP Voters, Oregon.
  - Public Opinion Polls, December 1965 (Box 64, Folder 699)
    Political Attitudes in New York State, December 1965.
  - "Hudson River Valley Survey", August 1966 (Box 64, Folder 700)
    Survey on issues affecting the Hudson Valley of New York.
  - New York State Candidate Standing, August 1966 (Box 64, Folder 701)
  - New York State Candidate Standing, September 1966 (Box 64, Folder 702)
  - New York State Public Attitudes - Rockefeller for Governor, June 1967 (Box 64, Folder 703)
  - New York State Public Attitudes - Transportation, Nuclear Power, June 1967 (Box 64, Folder 704)
  - "Attitudes on Selected New York State Issues", March 1968 (Box 65, Folder 705)
  - "Attitudes Toward Presidential Candidates", May 1968 (Box 65, Folder 706)
  - "National Attitudes on Several Presidential Campaign Issues", July 1968 (Box 65, Folder 707)
  - "Public Opinion in New York's 25th Congressional District", October 1968 (Box 65, Folder 708)
  - "The Rockefeller for President Advertising Campaign", July 1968 (Box 65, Folder 709)
  - "A Secret Ballot Study of Four Presidential Races and the U.S. Senate Race in Ohio", July 1968 (Box 65, Folder 710)
  - "A Study of Candidates and Issues in Ohio", June 1968 (Box 65, Folder 711)
  - "Trust & Confidence & Mental Image: A National Survey", July 1968 (Box 65, Folder 712)
  - "Opinion Survey of New York on Several Key Issues", June 1969 (Box 65, Folder 713)
  - "Standing of Possible Candidates for Governor in New York", June 1969 (Box 65, Folder 714)
  - "Survey of New York State Political Opinion", March 1969 (Box 65, Folder 715)
  - "Study of Potential Candidates for the U.S. Senate", October 1969 (Box 65, Folder 716)
  - National Media Analysis Reports - Reports 1, 4-6, 11-12, 14-15, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 717)
    Study of state areas and subjects of interest to direct NAR campaign efforts.
  - National Media Analysis Reports - Reports 21-29, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 718)